Party girls don't get hurt
Can't feel anything, when will Ilearn?
I push it down, push it down
I'm the one "for a good timecall"
Phone's blowin' up, ringin' mydoorbell
I feel the love, feel the love
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, drink
Throw 'em back 'til I lose count
I'm gonna swing from thechandelier, from the chandelier
I'm gonna live like tomorrowdoesn't exist
Like it doesn't exist
I'm gonna fly like a birdthrough the night, feel my tearsas they dry
I'm gonna swing from thechandelier, from the chandelier
But I'm holding on for dearlife, won't look down, won'topen my eyes
Keep my glass full until morninglight, 'cause I'm just holdingon for tonight
Help me, I'm holding on for dearlife, won't look down, won'topen my eyes
On for tonight
Sun is up, I'm a mess
Gotta get out now, gotta runfrom this
Here comes the shame, here comesthe shame
1, 2, 3, 1, 2, 3, drink
Throw 'em back 'til I lose count
I'm gonna swing from thechandelier, from the chandelier
I'm gonna live like tomorrowdoesn't exist
Like it doesn't exist
I'm gonna fly like a birdthrough the night, feel my tearsas they dry
I'm gonna swing from thechandelier, from the chandelier
But I'm holding on for dearlife, won't look down, won'topen my eyes
Keep my glass full until morninglight, 'cause I'm just holdingon for tonight
Help me, I'm holding on for dearlife, won't look down, won'topen my eyes
On for tonight
'Cause I'm just holding on fortonight
Oh, I'm just holding on fortonight
On for tonight
'Cause I'm just holding on fortonight
Oh, I'm just holding on fortonight
On for tonight
www.RentAnAdviser.com